http://www.thechristmaspalace.com/pages/privacy-policy

Wholesale Products
We consider your account information to be private, and we keep this information on a secure server to protect it from outside parties. We use the information only for the limited purposes of processing your orders, administering our site, and notifying you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you (only if you select to be included on out mailing list). We do not share your private information with anyone.
Privacy Policy
At The Christmas Palace, we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by The Christmas Palace Inc. In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at:
Privacy Matters c/o The Christmas Palace9820 NW 77th AveHialeah Gardens, FL 33016USA
Information we collect and how we use it
We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:
Information you provide
When you sign up for an account or promotions that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as our shopping cart programs, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
Cookies
When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. We may set a cookie in your browser when you visit a website and view or click on any products viewed by your browser.
Log information
When you access our services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
User communications
When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services
Affiliated sites
We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.
Links
We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our users browsing experience, customized content and advertising.
SAVE10%
SAVE 10%* ON YOUR ONLINE PURCHASE!
Sign up today and get a 10% discount you can use right away.
Be the first to find out about our specials.
Get design ideas from our expert team to inspire your holiday look.
*10% Off Code will be sent via email. Discount is not valid on "Last Chance" items or in combination with any other discount or offer.
In-store and online prices may vary. Prices will not be matched.
COPYRIGHT © 2020 THE CHRISTMAS PALACE. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
